# Frank Juval Quinones

Entrepreneurial, creative professional full of moxie, with a penchant for systems thinking, logistics, and servant leadership. With twenty-six years of experience in graphic design, brand development, web development, and animation, I've generated solutions for major corporations including Marriott, Universal, and NBC.

## **EXPERIENCE**

My versatility, resourcefulness, and initiative has served my previous employers very well. I'm the person they come to when they need help figuring out a particular piece of software, or if they need a different perspective in finding a solution. ◆ I'm always a student. I never stop learning. It's how one prevents becoming a dinosaur. Continual learning is also a way to improve one's workflow. ◆ It's important to put in the effort to build and nurture relationships because you never know what kind of amazing things can come from it. ◆ I've lead major projects, built teams, and influenced senior leadership. Please allow me the opportunity to put my experience in serving you.

#### CAREER HISTORY

Front End Developer/Digital Designer, Universal Parks & Resorts — 2013–2020 Web Designer, AffiliateManager.com — 2012-2013 Web Designer, Marriott Vacation Club — 2011–2012 Sr. Graphic Designer, Digital Daydream — 2009–2010 Publications Artist, VisitOrlando — 2004–2008 Graphic Designer, Tupperware — 2002–2004 Graphic Artist, Ames True Temper — 2002 Graphic Artist/animator, Various Employers — 1994–2002

#### **EDUCATION**

Santa Fe College, Gainesville, Florida — A.A.S. in Graphic Design, 2001 University of Central Florida, Orlando Florida — Traditional Animation Program, 1997-1998 New World School of the Arts, Miami, Florida — Fine Arts Program, 1994-1996 Miami-Dade College — General Education, 1991-1993

### **SKILLS**

Adobe Creative Cloud: I've used Adobe since the very first Photoshop and Illustrator, to the Creative Suite, and Creative Cloud. InDesign, After Effects, Animate, Acrobat, and a few other Adobe apps.

Code: HTML, CSS, JS, Git/Github, jQuery, GreenSock JS, CLI, Grunt, Gulp, Rest API, Sass, MarkDown, and more.

Tools: InVision/InVision Studio, Sketch, Slack, WordPress & other CMS, Figma, Abstract, After Effects, and more.

Other: Microsoft Office, Google products, photography, A/B testing, and more.

If you're fixated on a degree and completely miss my 26 years of real world experience, then you really don't get it and this won't work.